

JUAN MANUEL LÓPEZ ARRIETA

About me

My name is Juan Manuel López, and I am 18 years old. I am currently studying a VET in computer science at Lacetània. During my free time, I enjoy going to the gym, playing video games, reading, and spending time with my friends.

Although I am still quite new to the working world, I am eager to gain experience. Unfortunately, my age has prevented me from working in the past. However, this year I have already gained a little experience while doing Work Center Training (FCT) at my current high school this year, which will allow me to gain valuable work experience.

Education

2018 - 2022 General Certificate of Secondary Education (GCSE)

Institut d'Auro, Santpedor

2022 - 2024 Vocational Education and Training (VET)

Microcomputer systems and networks

Institut Làcetania, Manresa

2024 - Act Advanced Vocational Training (AVT)

Multiplatform Application Development

Universitat de Vic (UVIC)

Experience

2023 - 2024

Work Center Training (FCT)
AMPANS. Sant Fruitos

- Maintenance of computer equipment
- Microsoft Office applications
- Software installation

Contact

+34 68067 84 89

juanmanuellopezarrieta@gmail.com

03 - 04 - 2006

Vic, 08500

@juanitooo_2006

Languages

• **English** B2 - Cambridge

• Spanish Mother Tongue

• Catalan Mother Tongue

Skills

- Web Development (HTML, CSS)
- Video Editing
- PC , Laptop, Smartphones Maintenance
- Graphic Design
- Microsoft Office Apps

Another Data

Time Availability: Only Evenings

Driver License: On progress

Personal Car: Yes



JUAN MANUEL LÓPEZ ARRIETA

Sobre mi

Mi nombre es Juan Manuel López y tengo 18 años. Actualmente estoy estudiando un CFGM de informática en Lacetània. Durante mi tiempo libre, me gusta ir al gimnasio, jugar videojuegos, leer y pasar tiempo con mis amigos.

Aunque todavía soy bastante nuevo en el mundo laboral, tengo muchas ganas de adquirir experiencia. Desafortunadamente, mi edad me ha impedido trabajar en el pasado. Sin embargo, este año ya adquirí un poco de experiencia mientras realizaba Formación en Centros de Trabajo (FCT) en mi actual escuela secundaria este año, lo que me permitirá adquirir una valiosa experiencia laboral.

Estudios

2018 - 2022 Educación Secundaria Obligatoria (ESO)

Institut d'Auro, Santpedor

2022 - 2024 Ciclo Formativo de Grado Medio (CFGM)

Sistemes microinformàtics i xarxes

Institut Làcetania, Manresa

2024 - Act Ciclo Formativo de Grado Superior (CFGS)

Desarrollo de Aplicaciones Multiplataforma

Universitat de Vic (UVIC)

Experiencia

2023 - 2024 Formación en Centros de Trabajo (FCT)
AMPANS. Sant Fruitos

- Mantenimiento de equipos informáticos.
- Aplicaciones de Microsoft Office
- Instalación de software

Contacto

+34 68067 84 89

juanmanuellopezarrieta@gmail.com

03 - 04 - 2006

Vic. 08500

@juanitooo_2006

Idiomas

• English B2 - Cambridge

• Español Nativo

• Catalán Nativo

Hablilidades

- Web Development (HTML, CSS)
- Video Editing
- PC , Laptop, Smartphones Maintenance
- Graphic Design
- Microsoft Office Apps

Otros datos

Disponibilidad horaria: Todo el Dia

Carnet de Conducir: En progreso

Coche Propio: Si